icsource.com 2015-12-12

# IC Source | Home

**IC Source Privacy Policy**

The information we collect on our website and webpages is only used for practices that are consistent with the context of the transaction you are engaging in with us and consistent with your relationship with us.  IC Source uses collected information for the following general purposes: products and services provision, billing, identification and authentication, services improvement, contact, and research.  The information is used to improve the content of our Web pages and the quality of our service, when we have your permission, or under the following circumstances:

  * It is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of Terms of Service of the specific application, or as otherwise required by law.
  * We will share your information with wholly owned sister companies. In this event, IC Source will notify you before information about you becomes subject to a different privacy policy.

IC Source does not sell your personal information to third parties for any purpose.

**INFORMATION COLLECTED**

We collect two kinds of information about our online visitors through our websites and webpages: non-personal and personal information. 

The non-personal information we collect includes:

  * device ID or unique identifier, device type, geo-location information, computer and connection information, statistics on page views, searches, traffic to and from the sites, referral URL, ad data, IP address, and standard web log information, 
  * anonymous information collected through our use cookies and web beacons

We collect personal information that can identify a visitor, such as name or address only when you voluntarily provide it, and we use that information solely for purposes that are clearly identified on our sites and webpages.  

**COOKIES**

**How We Use “Cookies” on Our Websites**

IC Source may place electronic “cookies” in the browser files of your computer when you access an IC Source website. Cookies are pieces of information that an IC Source website transfers to your computer to enable our systems to recognize your browser and to tailor the information on our websites to your interests.  For example, if you previously visited an IC Source website and accessed your account information or inquired about particular services over the website, cookies enable us to present information tailored to your account and/or those particular interests the next time you visit the website. Moreover, IC Source or our third party service providers or business partners may place cookies on your computer’s hard drive that can be matched to other personal information we maintain about you to pre-populate certain online forms for your convenience.  We also use cookies to analyze visitors’ use of our websites. This analysis helps us better understand which areas of our sites are most useful and popular so we can plan improvements and updates accordingly. 

Many web browsers are automatically set to accept cookies. You may change your computer’s web browser settings to either reject cookies or notify you when a cookie is about to be placed on your computer. Please note, however, that rejecting cookies while visiting any of our websites may result in certain parts of the website not operating as efficiently as if the cookies were allowed. For example, if you reject cookies from our websites, you may not be able to access a preferred location, view a customized default home page or pre-populated form, or easily access your recently visited links or pages. 

**DATA STORAGE**

IC Source uses third party vendors and hosting partners to provide the necessary hardware, software, networking, storage, and related technology required to run our services.  

**IC Source** does not seek or knowingly collect personal information from children.   

Access to pages with content specific to vendors, brokers and customers is password-protected and requires registration. Personal information acquired through registration is kept confidential and will not be disclosed to third parties except as may be permitted or required by law.  Depending upon your relationship with us, you may receive other privacy notices from us providing additional detail about our privacy practices. 

We may offer blogs, online forums or other interactive features on our websites and webpages that enable consumers to share information about our services or other issues of interest.  You should be aware that any communications you submit or post to any such interactive features on our websites and webpages may be viewable by other participants or users of our websites and webpages.  Therefore, you acknowledge and understand that you have no expectation of privacy or confidentiality in the content you submit for such interactive features, whether or not it contains personal information about you. 

**Security of Internet Communications**

The Internet is not a secure medium. We employ administrative, technical and physical safeguards to protect personal information but cannot assume any responsibility for any harm, loss or damage you may experience from transmission of information by or to IC Source over the Internet. 

**How to Access and Correct Information Provided on IC Source Websites and Webpages**

If you would like to access and correct personal information you have submitted to us through one of our sites or on one of our webpages, please send a letter to the address below requesting to see your information.  We will be happy to make corrections whenever possible but may not be able to provide information relating to investigations, claims, litigation and other matters. 

Please address requests to:

IC Source   
Attention: Privacy Inquiries  
P.O. Box 5166  
Saratoga Springs NY 12866  
Telephone: 1-518-885-8880  
Email: [privacyinquiries@IC Source.com](mailto:privacyinquiries@icsource.com)

**CHANGES**

IC Source may periodically update this policy. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by sending a notice to the primary email address specified in your IC Source service primary account holder account or by placing a prominent notice on our site. 

**Consent**

By using this site, or any of our websites or webpages, you signify your consent to this Internet Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use this site. 

We reserve the right, at our discretion, to update, change, modify, add or remove portions of this policy from time to time.  You can always find out about any such changes, and access the most current version of this Internet Privacy Policy, by clicking on “Privacy Policy” on the homepage of any IC Source website. 

**Information collected from visitors from outside the United States** If you are visiting the IC Source website from outside the United States and provide us with personal information, please note that your personal information will be transferred, stored and processed within the United States. Additionally, IC Source may transfer your personal information to other countries, for example because a server or third party service provider is located there. The data protection and privacy laws of other countries, including the United States, may not afford you the same level of protection as those in your own country.  IC Source will take appropriate steps to protect your information. **

By doing business or interacting with IC Source, you are consenting to the transfer, storage, and processing of your personal information to and within facilities located in the United States and other facility locations selected by IC Source.

**
